Maxim Zanoga

Personal info

Rivne, Ukraine

zanoga.maxim@gmail.com

tel: +380971016471 / skype: zanoga.maxim

GitHub: https://github.com/ZanMax

Profile

Software engineer with more than 10 years of experience in commercial web applications development based on microservices architecture. Has advanced knowledge in Python programming language including different frameworks; interested in Go Land. Experienced in creating business needs solving systems from scratch and expanding them further according to requirements. Worked with Docker, Kubernetes, and different cloud providers. Was involved in the support of product infrastructure.

Work experience

Feb 2018 - Present

Senior Python Developer

Raise.Band

E-commerce, Affiliate marketing, and Education

Architecture, WebServices, MicroServices, (Python, Go, Flask, FastApi), Al

(GPT-2), Docker, Kubernetes, AWS

Jun 2014 - Feb 2018

Senior Python Developer

Learnify OU

Web Development, Marketing Research, and Academic consulting.

Architecture, WebServices, MicroServices, (Python, Flask)

March 2013 - Jun 2014

Python Developer

SoftServe / Cisco

Networking, Cloud, and Cybersecurity Solutions

WebServices, MicroServices, Parsers (Python, Flask)

Sep 2010 - March 2013

Software Developer

Novus

Retail industry

WebServices (C#), Mobile App (Android), MicroServices (Python)

Education

Master of computer science / Rivne State Humanitarian University

2004 – 2009

Skills

Backend: Python (Strong), Go (Middle)

Frontend: JavaScript / VUE JS (Middle)

Testing: PyTest, Selenium, JMeter, Robot

Databases: Relational (MySQL, PostgreSQL),

Framework, etc.

NoSQL (MongoDB, Redis)

Cloud Providers: AWS

Version Control: Git

Other: Docker, Docker-Compose, Kubernetes, Message Brokers (RabbitMQ), CI/CD (Jenkins),

Shell, Network, etc.

Language: English (intermediate)